const THEMES = {

    // displayname => replace "_" with " " and css capitalize
    BOTH_WHITE: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#e8e8e8",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#d0d0d0",
        "--key-color-front": "#b6b6b6",
        "--key-color-side": "#a2a2a2",
        "--key-color-back": "#919191",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    BOTH_DARK: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#2a2a2a",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#1c1c1c",
        "--key-color-front": "#151515",
        "--key-color-side": "#0c0c0c",
        "--key-color-back": "#000000",
        "--key-font-color": "#c0cae1"
    },
    BOTH_CATPPUCCIN_MOCHA: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#3b405e",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#2e324b",
        "--key-color-front": "#202334",
        "--key-color-side": "#1e2131",
        "--key-color-back": "#171926",
        "--key-font-color": "#C6D0F5"
    },
    DARK_CATPPUCCIN_LIGHT: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#C5CFF5",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#bfc7ec",
        "--key-color-front": "#B7BDF8",
        "--key-color-side": "#8AADF4",
        "--key-color-back": "#6e99d2",
        "--key-font-color": "#4b4546"
    },
    BOTH_CLEAN_WHITE:{
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#D0D8E0",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#BEC8D0",
        "--key-color-front": "#A0A8B0",
        "--key-color-side": "#909898",
        "--key-color-back": "#808888",
        "--key-font-color": "#303030"
    },
    BOTH_HIGH_CONTRAST: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#000000",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#212121",
        "--key-color-front": "#3a3a3a",
        "--key-color-side": "#2c2c2c",
        "--key-color-back": "#111111",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"

    },
    BOTH_SILVER: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#BAB9BE",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#A0A0A5",
        "--key-color-front": "#82858E",
        "--key-color-side": "#434346",
        "--key-color-back": "#343635",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    BOTH_FOREST_MIST: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#7DAE9E",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#6A9A8B",
        "--key-color-front": "#5C8D76",
        "--key-color-side": "#3A5A40",
        "--key-color-back": "#2F3E46",
        "--key-font-color": "#E0E0E0"
    },
    BOTH_LAVENDER_DREAMS: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#E0B0FF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#C18EE0",
        "--key-color-front": "#9A8CFF",
        "--key-color-side": "#7B68EE",
        "--key-color-back": "#4B0082",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    BOTH_DEEP_OCEAN: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#64B5F6",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#42A5F5",
        "--key-color-front": "#1E88E5",
        "--key-color-side": "#1565C0",
        "--key-color-back": "#0D47A1",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    BOTH_BACK_IN_THE_OLD_DAYS: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#D4D3BF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#D6D0C0",
        "--key-color-front": "#B0AE97",
        "--key-color-side": "#7D7A5C",
        "--key-color-back": "#4d4a37",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    }
};